{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "2(4x + 5)(x + 1)/(2x + 1)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 5)/3(2x + 1))/((4x + 7)/6(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 5)/3(2x + 1) * 6(x + 1)/(4x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 1) + 2/3)/(1/2(x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(6x + 23)(x + 3)/2(2x + 7)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 23)/2(2x + 7))/((x + 6)/3(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 23)/2(2x + 7) * 3(x + 3)/(x + 6)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 7) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 3) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 11)(x + 3)/9(3x + 2)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 11)/3(3x + 2))/(3(x + 4)/2(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 11)/3(3x + 2) * 2(x + 3)/3(x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 2) + 1/3)/(3/2(x + 3) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8(x + 4)(x + 1)/3(2x + 5)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(4(x + 4)/3(2x + 5))/((4x + 5)/2(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n4(x + 4)/3(2x + 5) * 2(x + 1)/(4x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 5) + 2/3)/(1/2(x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 17)(2x + 1)/8(2x + 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 17)/2(2x + 5))/(4(x + 1)/(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 17)/2(2x + 5) * (2x + 1)/4(x + 1)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 5) + 3/2)/(2/(2x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x + 13)(x + 4)/4(x + 1)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 13)/6(x + 1))/(2(x + 7)/3(x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 13)/6(x + 1) * 3(x + 4)/2(x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 1) + 2/3)/(2/(x + 4) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x + 6)(x + 2)/(x + 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(x + 6)/3(x + 3))/((x + 3)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n2(x + 6)/3(x + 3) * 3(x + 2)/(x + 3)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 3) + 2/3)/(1/3(x + 2) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 13)(x + 1)/(3x + 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 13)/3(3x + 4))/((x + 4)/3(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 13)/3(3x + 4) * 3(x + 1)/(x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 4) + 1/3)/(1/(x + 1) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(2x + 9)(x + 2)/3(x + 3)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 9)/3(x + 3))/((3x + 10)/2(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 9)/3(x + 3) * 2(x + 2)/(3x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 3) + 2/3)/(2/(x + 2) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(6x + 17)(x + 2)/3(3x + 7)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 17)/3(3x + 7))/((3x + 8)/2(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 17)/3(3x + 7) * 2(x + 2)/(3x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 7) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 2) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x + 13)(3x + 5)/9(2x + 5)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 13)/3(2x + 5))/(3(3x + 7)/2(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 13)/3(2x + 5) * 2(3x + 5)/3(3x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 5) + 2/3)/(3/(3x + 5) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 17)(2x + 3)/3(3x + 4)(6x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 17)/3(3x + 4))/((6x + 11)/(2x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 17)/3(3x + 4) * (2x + 3)/(6x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 4) + 2/3)/(2/(2x + 3) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6(3x + 5)(3x + 7)/(2x + 3)(3x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 5)/(2x + 3))/((3x + 13)/3(3x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) * 3(3x + 7)/(3x + 13)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 3) + 3)/(2/(3x + 7) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 22)(3x + 5)/3(x + 2)(9x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 22)/6(x + 2))/((9x + 19)/2(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 22)/6(x + 2) * 2(3x + 5)/(9x + 19)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/3(x + 2) + 3/2)/(2/(3x + 5) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 3)(3x + 2)/(x + 1)(9x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 3)/(x + 1))/((9x + 8)/(3x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 3)/(x + 1) * (3x + 2)/(9x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 1) + 2)/(2/(3x + 2) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(2x + 11)(x + 2)/2(2x + 7)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 11)/2(2x + 7))/((x + 8)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 11)/2(2x + 7) * 3(x + 2)/(x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 7) + 1/2)/(2/(x + 2) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 5)(x + 2)/12(x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 5)/6(x + 1))/(2(x + 3)/(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 5)/6(x + 1) * (x + 2)/2(x + 3)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/3(x + 1) + 1/2)/(2/(x + 2) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x + 11)(2x + 1)/(x + 2)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 11)/2(x + 2))/((2x + 5)/2(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 11)/2(x + 2) * 2(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 2) + 2)/(2/(2x + 1) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4(x + 4)(2x + 7)/3(2x + 5)(2x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(x + 4)/3(2x + 5))/((2x + 13)/2(2x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n2(x + 4)/3(2x + 5) * 2(2x + 7)/(2x + 13)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 5) + 1/3)/(3/(2x + 7) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(9x + 4)(x + 2)/(3x + 1)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 4)/(3x + 1))/((2x + 7)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 4)/(3x + 1) * 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 1) + 3)/(1/(x + 2) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(9x + 7)(x + 6)/2(3x + 1)(x + 12)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 7)/2(3x + 1))/((x + 12)/3(x + 6))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 7)/2(3x + 1) * 3(x + 6)/(x + 12)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 1) + 3/2)/(2/(x + 6) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/3(3x + 2)(6x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 5)/3(3x + 2))/((6x + 5)/(3x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 5)/3(3x + 2) * (3x + 1)/(6x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 2) + 1/3)/(3/(3x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 5)/(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 19)/2(x + 3))/((6x + 19)/2(2x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 19)/2(x + 3) * 2(2x + 5)/(6x + 19)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/2(x + 3) + 3)/(2/(2x + 5) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 4)(x + 3)/(x + 2)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(x + 4)/2(x + 2))/((3x + 10)/2(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n3(x + 4)/2(x + 2) * 2(x + 3)/(3x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 2) + 3/2)/(1/2(x + 3) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 16)(3x + 4)/(x + 5)(6x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 16)/(x + 5))/((6x + 17)/3(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 16)/(x + 5) * 3(3x + 4)/(6x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 5) + 3)/(3/(3x + 4) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 9)(2x + 1)/8(x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 9)/2(x + 5))/(4(x + 2)/3(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 9)/2(x + 5) * 3(2x + 1)/4(x + 2)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 5) + 1/2)/(2/(2x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(x + 6)(x + 2)/2(x + 4)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(x + 6)/2(x + 4))/((2x + 7)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n3(x + 6)/2(x + 4) * 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 4) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 2) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(2x + 5)(x + 2)/(2x + 3)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(2x + 5)/2(2x + 3))/((3x + 8)/2(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n3(2x + 5)/2(2x + 3) * 2(x + 2)/(3x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 3) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 2) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 5)(x + 7)/4(x + 2)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 5)/2(x + 2))/(2(x + 10)/3(x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 5)/2(x + 2) * 3(x + 7)/2(x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 2) + 1/2)/(2/(x + 7) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(x + 2)(3x + 5)/(x + 1)(6x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(x + 2)/(x + 1))/((6x + 13)/3(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n3(x + 2)/(x + 1) * 3(3x + 5)/(6x + 13)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 1) + 3)/(1/(3x + 5) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x + 11)(x + 2)/3(2x + 1)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 11)/3(2x + 1))/((x + 8)/2(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 11)/3(2x + 1) * 2(x + 2)/(x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 1) + 2/3)/(3/(x + 2) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4(3x + 5)(3x + 7)/(2x + 3)(9x + 25)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 5)/(2x + 3))/((9x + 25)/2(3x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) * 2(3x + 7)/(9x + 25)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 3) + 3)/(2/(3x + 7) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x + 13)(2x + 3)/(x + 3)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 13)/2(x + 3))/((2x + 7)/2(2x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 13)/2(x + 3) * 2(2x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/2(x + 3) + 2)/(2/(2x + 3) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4(3x + 10)(x + 6)/3(3x + 7)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 10)/3(3x + 7))/((x + 10)/2(x + 6))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 10)/3(3x + 7) * 2(x + 6)/(x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 7) + 2/3)/(2/(x + 6) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "18(x + 2)(x + 3)/(x + 1)(2x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(x + 2)/(x + 1))/((2x + 15)/6(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n3(x + 2)/(x + 1) * 6(x + 3)/(2x + 15)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 1) + 3)/(3/2(x + 3) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 11)(3x + 5)/2(x + 5)(9x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 11)/2(x + 5))/((9x + 17)/(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 11)/2(x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(9x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 5) + 1/2)/(2/(3x + 5) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 10)(x + 1)/(3x + 7)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 10)/3(3x + 7))/((2x + 5)/3(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 10)/3(3x + 7) * 3(x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 7) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(2x + 7)(3x + 4)/2(x + 3)(6x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(2x + 7)/2(x + 3))/((6x + 11)/3(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n3(2x + 7)/2(x + 3) * 3(3x + 4)/(6x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 3) + 3)/(1/(3x + 4) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 10)(3x + 4)/3(x + 4)(9x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 10)/3(x + 4))/((9x + 14)/(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 10)/3(x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(9x + 14)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 4) + 1/3)/(2/(3x + 4) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8(x + 3)(3x + 7)/(2x + 5)(9x + 25)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(4(x + 3)/(2x + 5))/((9x + 25)/2(3x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n4(x + 3)/(2x + 5) * 2(3x + 7)/(9x + 25)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 5) + 2)/(2/(3x + 7) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 25)(3x + 2)/12(2x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 25)/2(2x + 7))/(6(x + 1)/(3x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 25)/2(2x + 7) * (3x + 2)/6(x + 1)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 7) + 3/2)/(2/(3x + 2) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4(3x + 7)/3(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(6(x + 3)/(2x + 5))/(9(x + 3)/2(3x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n6(x + 3)/(2x + 5) * 2(3x + 7)/9(x + 3)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 5) + 3)/(3/(3x + 7) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x + 9)(2x + 1)/3(2x + 3)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 9)/3(2x + 3))/((2x + 5)/2(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 9)/3(2x + 3) * 2(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 3) + 2/3)/(2/(2x + 1) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/9(x + 1)(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 4)/3(x + 1))/(3(2x + 1)/(3x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 4)/3(x + 1) * (3x + 1)/3(2x + 1)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/3(x + 1) + 2)/(1/(3x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 4)(2x + 7)/4(x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 4)/(x + 1))/(4(x + 4)/(2x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 4)/(x + 1) * (2x + 7)/4(x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 1) + 3)/(2/(2x + 7) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8(x + 4)(x + 3)/(2x + 7)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(4(x + 4)/(2x + 7))/((3x + 10)/2(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n4(x + 4)/(2x + 7) * 2(x + 3)/(3x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 7) + 2)/(1/2(x + 3) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 23)(x + 1)/3(3x + 7)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 23)/3(3x + 7))/((3x + 4)/(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 23)/3(3x + 7) * (x + 1)/(3x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 7) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 1) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(2x + 11)(x + 1)/(x + 5)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 11)/(x + 5))/((x + 3)/2(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 11)/(x + 5) * 2(x + 1)/(x + 3)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 5) + 2)/(1/(x + 1) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 17)(2x + 7)/2(x + 5)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 17)/(x + 5))/(2(3x + 11)/(2x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 17)/(x + 5) * (2x + 7)/2(3x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 5) + 3)/(1/(2x + 7) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6(3x + 11)(3x + 7)/(2x + 7)(6x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 11)/(2x + 7))/((6x + 17)/3(3x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 11)/(2x + 7) * 3(3x + 7)/(6x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 7) + 3)/(1/(3x + 7) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x + 13)(2x + 1)/3(x + 7)(6x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 13)/3(x + 7))/((6x + 7)/2(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 13)/3(x + 7) * 2(2x + 1)/(6x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 7) + 1/3)/(2/(2x + 1) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 22)(x + 6)/2(x + 2)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 22)/6(x + 2))/((x + 9)/3(x + 6))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 22)/6(x + 2) * 3(x + 6)/(x + 9)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/3(x + 2) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 6) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(6x + 5)(x + 3)/(3x + 2)(2x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 5)/(3x + 2))/((2x + 15)/3(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 5)/(3x + 2) * 3(x + 3)/(2x + 15)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 2) + 2)/(3/(x + 3) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 13)(x + 3)/(3x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 13)/(3x + 5))/((2x + 9)/(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 13)/(3x + 5) * (x + 3)/(2x + 9)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 5) + 2)/(3/(x + 3) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(x + 8)(2x + 3)/3(2x + 7)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(x + 8)/3(2x + 7))/((4x + 7)/(2x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n2(x + 8)/3(2x + 7) * (2x + 3)/(4x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 7) + 1/3)/(1/(2x + 3) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(x + 9)(x + 1)/2(x + 7)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(x + 9)/2(x + 7))/((2x + 11)/3(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n3(x + 9)/2(x + 7) * 3(x + 1)/(2x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 7) + 3/2)/(3/(x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(4x + 15)(x + 7)/9(2x + 3)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 15)/3(2x + 3))/(3(x + 8)/(x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 15)/3(2x + 3) * (x + 7)/3(x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 3) + 2/3)/(3/(x + 7) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 4)(3x + 2)/3(x + 3)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 4)/2(x + 3))/(3(3x + 4)/2(3x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 4)/2(x + 3) * 2(3x + 2)/3(3x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/2(x + 3) + 1/2)/(3/(3x + 2) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(6x + 13)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 13)/3(3x + 2))/((2x + 11)/3(2x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 13)/3(3x + 2) * 3(2x + 5)/(2x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 2) + 2/3)/(2/(2x + 5) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 9)(x + 5)/3(x + 6)(3x + 16)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 9)/3(x + 6))/((3x + 16)/(x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 9)/3(x + 6) * (x + 5)/(3x + 16)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 6) + 1/3)/(1/(x + 5) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 11)(x + 7)/(x + 2)(2x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 11)/3(x + 2))/((2x + 17)/3(x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 11)/3(x + 2) * 3(x + 7)/(2x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 2) + 1/3)/(1/(x + 7) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x + 17)(x + 4)/3(2x + 7)(3x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 17)/3(2x + 7))/((3x + 14)/2(x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 17)/3(2x + 7) * 2(x + 4)/(3x + 14)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 7) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 4) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(4x + 3)(x + 2)/(2x + 1)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 3)/(2x + 1))/((x + 4)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 3)/(2x + 1) * 3(x + 2)/(x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(2x + 1) + 2)/(2/3(x + 2) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 11)(x + 7)/2(x + 3)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 11)/2(x + 3))/((x + 10)/3(x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 11)/2(x + 3) * 3(x + 7)/(x + 10)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 3) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 7) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 2)(x + 5)/(3x + 1)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 2)/(3x + 1))/((2x + 11)/(x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 2)/(3x + 1) * (x + 5)/(2x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 1) + 2)/(1/(x + 5) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 9)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(6x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 9)/3(2x + 3))/((6x + 5)/3(3x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 9)/3(2x + 3) * 3(3x + 1)/(6x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 3) + 1/3)/(1/(3x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 14)(3x + 4)/(x + 4)(9x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 14)/(x + 4))/((9x + 13)/(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 14)/(x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(9x + 13)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 4) + 3)/(1/(3x + 4) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(2x + 13)(x + 5)/3(2x + 7)(3x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 13)/3(2x + 7))/((3x + 17)/2(x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 13)/3(2x + 7) * 2(x + 5)/(3x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 7) + 1/3)/(1/(x + 5) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 11)(x + 1)/9(3x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 11)/3(3x + 5))/(3(x + 2)/(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 11)/3(3x + 5) * (x + 1)/3(x + 2)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 5) + 1/3)/(3/(x + 1) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(x + 8)(2x + 5)/2(x + 6)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 8)/2(x + 6))/((2x + 11)/3(2x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 8)/2(x + 6) * 3(2x + 5)/(2x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 6) + 1/2)/(2/(2x + 5) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 9)(x + 7)/9(x + 6)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 9)/3(x + 6))/(3(x + 8)/(x + 7))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 9)/3(x + 6) * (x + 7)/3(x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 6) + 1/3)/(3/(x + 7) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9(2x + 5)/4(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(3(2x + 5)/2(x + 2))/(2(3x + 7)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n3(2x + 5)/2(x + 2) * 3(x + 2)/2(3x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 2) + 3)/(2/3(x + 2) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 13)(x + 1)/(x + 3)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 13)/2(x + 3))/((3x + 5)/2(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 13)/2(x + 3) * 2(x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 3) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 1) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 10)(x + 5)/4(x + 3)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 10)/2(x + 3))/(2(x + 8)/3(x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 10)/2(x + 3) * 3(x + 5)/2(x + 8)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/2(x + 3) + 3/2)/(2/(x + 5) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 13)(2x + 3)/(x + 5)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 13)/(x + 5))/((4x + 9)/(2x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 13)/(x + 5) * (2x + 3)/(4x + 9)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 5) + 2)/(3/(2x + 3) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 5)(3x + 4)/3(x + 1)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 5)/2(x + 1))/(3(x + 2)/2(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 5)/2(x + 1) * 2(3x + 4)/3(x + 2)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 1) + 3/2)/(1/(3x + 4) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 7)/2(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 7)/2(x + 1))/((2x + 3)/(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 7)/2(x + 1) * (x + 1)/(2x + 3)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 1) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(6x + 19)(x + 3)/2(2x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((6x + 19)/2(2x + 5))/((2x + 9)/3(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(6x + 19)/2(2x + 5) * 3(x + 3)/(2x + 9)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(2x + 5) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 3) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(2x + 7)(3x + 2)/(x + 2)(6x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 7)/(x + 2))/((6x + 7)/3(3x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 7)/(x + 2) * 3(3x + 2)/(6x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(x + 2) + 2)/(1/(3x + 2) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1/3", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 11)/6(x + 2))/((4x + 11)/2(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 11)/6(x + 2) * 2(x + 2)/(4x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/2(x + 2) + 2/3)/(3/2(x + 2) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(4x + 23)(x + 6)/3(2x + 7)(x + 12)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 23)/3(2x + 7))/((x + 12)/2(x + 6))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 23)/3(2x + 7) * 2(x + 6)/(x + 12)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(2x + 7) + 2/3)/(3/(x + 6) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 9)(3x + 2)/3(x + 3)(6x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 9)/3(x + 3))/((6x + 7)/(3x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 9)/3(x + 3) * (3x + 2)/(6x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 3) + 2/3)/(3/(3x + 2) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 8)/4(x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 8)/2(x + 2))/(2(x + 5)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 8)/2(x + 2) * 3(x + 2)/2(x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 2) + 3/2)/(2/(x + 2) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 5)(x + 3)/2(x + 1)(x + 12)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 5)/2(x + 1))/((x + 12)/3(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 5)/2(x + 1) * 3(x + 3)/(x + 12)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 1) + 3/2)/(3/(x + 3) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 11)(2x + 3)/3(3x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 11)/3(3x + 5))/((2x + 9)/2(2x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 11)/3(3x + 5) * 2(2x + 3)/(2x + 9)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 5) + 1/3)/(3/(2x + 3) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 3)(3x + 5)/(x + 1)(9x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 3)/(x + 1))/((9x + 17)/(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 3)/(x + 1) * (3x + 5)/(9x + 17)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 1) + 2)/(2/(3x + 5) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(4x + 11)(x + 3)/(x + 2)(4x + 21)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((4x + 11)/2(x + 2))/((4x + 21)/6(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(4x + 11)/2(x + 2) * 6(x + 3)/(4x + 21)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/2(x + 2) + 2)/(3/2(x + 3) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6(9x + 5)(x + 1)/(3x + 1)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 5)/(3x + 1))/((3x + 5)/6(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 5)/(3x + 1) * 6(x + 1)/(3x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 1) + 3)/(1/3(x + 1) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 20)(x + 3)/6(x + 2)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 20)/6(x + 2))/((2x + 7)/(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 20)/6(x + 2) * (x + 3)/(2x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/3(x + 2) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 3) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 10)(2x + 1)/(x + 1)(4x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 10)/3(x + 1))/((4x + 11)/3(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 10)/3(x + 1) * 3(2x + 1)/(4x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/3(x + 1) + 3)/(3/(2x + 1) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 7)(3x + 5)/2(x + 1)(3x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 7)/2(x + 1))/((3x + 14)/3(3x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 7)/2(x + 1) * 3(3x + 5)/(3x + 14)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 1) + 3/2)/(3/(3x + 5) + 1/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(2x + 9)/3(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 9)/3(x + 3))/((3x + 11)/2(x + 3))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 9)/3(x + 3) * 2(x + 3)/(3x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 3) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 3) + 3/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3(3x + 5)(x + 2)/2(3x + 1)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 5)/2(3x + 1))/((2x + 7)/3(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 5)/2(3x + 1) * 3(x + 2)/(2x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 1) + 1/2)/(1/(x + 2) + 2/3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(2x + 11)(2x + 1)/12(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((2x + 11)/3(x + 4))/(4(x + 1)/(2x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(2x + 11)/3(x + 4) * (2x + 1)/4(x + 1)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(x + 4) + 2/3)/(2/(2x + 1) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(3x + 13)(3x + 4)/4(3x + 7)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((3x + 13)/2(3x + 7))/(2(3x + 5)/(3x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(3x + 13)/2(3x + 7) * (3x + 4)/2(3x + 5)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(3/(3x + 7) + 1/2)/(2/(3x + 4) + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 23)(x + 1)/2(3x + 7)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 23)/2(3x + 7))/((3x + 4)/(x + 1))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 23)/2(3x + 7) * (x + 1)/(3x + 4)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 7) + 3/2)/(1/(x + 1) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(9x + 7)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 7)/(3x + 2))/((2x + 11)/2(2x + 5))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 7)/(3x + 2) * 2(2x + 5)/(2x + 11)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/(3x + 2) + 3)/(3/(2x + 5) + 1/2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2(3x + 8)(x + 2)/3(3x + 5)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n(2(3x + 8)/3(3x + 5))/((3x + 7)/(x + 2))\nFlip the divisor\n2(3x + 8)/3(3x + 5) * (x + 2)/(3x + 7)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(3x + 5) + 2/3)/(1/(x + 2) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(x + 8)(x + 4)/3(x + 2)(3x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((x + 8)/3(x + 2))/((3x + 14)/(x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(x + 8)/3(x + 2) * (x + 4)/(3x + 14)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(2/(x + 2) + 1/3)/(2/(x + 4) + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "(9x + 11)(x + 4)/9(x + 1)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n((9x + 11)/6(x + 1))/(3(x + 6)/2(x + 4))\nFlip the divisor\n(9x + 11)/6(x + 1) * 2(x + 4)/3(x + 6)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify", "question": "Simplify:\n(1/3(x + 1) + 3/2)/(3/(x + 4) + 3/2)", "type": "text"}
]}